=Love Lurking=
=الحب الكامن=
=Episode 15=
=الحلقة 15=
Let me get it.
دعني أحصل عليه.
Okay.
تمام.
Weren't you supposed to choose a wedding dress today?
ألم يكن من المفترض أن تختاري فستان الزفاف اليوم؟
Go first.
اذهب أولا.
I'll be there soon.
سأكون هناك قريبا.
Okay.
تمام.
Then come early.
ثم تعال مبكرا.
Won't you come out?
ألن تخرج؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'll see you out.
سأراك في الخارج.
Give me back my phone.
أعطني هاتفي مرة أخرى.
Delete the video.
حذف الفيديو
Help me find Zhao Yan first.
ساعدني في العثور على تشاو يان أولاً.
Then I'll delete the video.
ثم سأحذف الفيديو.
(Li Weiwei)
(لي ويوي)
Are you going to delete it or not?
هل ستحذفه أم لا؟
No way.
مستحيل.
Don't blame me for speaking up.
لا تلوموني على التحدث.
What do you want to do?
ماذا تريد أن تفعل؟
Nian?
لنا؟
Give me back my phone.
أعطني هاتفي مرة أخرى.
Give it back.
أعيدها.
Nian?
لنا؟
Why aren't you talking?
لماذا لا تتكلم؟
I saw the bar's surveillance.
لقد رأيت مراقبة البار.
It was Song Qian who took you away.
لقد كان سونغ تشيان هو الذي أخذك بعيدًا.
You didn't sleep with him, did you?
لم تنم معه، أليس كذلك؟
You really seduced him?
هل أغويته حقا؟
Li Weiwei, shut up.
لي ويوي، اصمت.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Why are you upset?
لماذا انت منزعج؟
Didn't you say before that although he's annoying,
ألم تقل من قبل أنه على الرغم من أنه مزعج،
at least he looks alright?
على الأقل يبدو بخير؟
You must have enjoyed it, right?
لا بد أنك استمتعت بذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Li Weiwei, you...
لي ويوي، أنت...
Why are you mad?
لماذا انت مجنون؟
Are you dissatisfied with him?
هل أنت غير راضٍ عنه؟
What about me dissatisfies you?
ما الذي يزعجك فيّ؟
Mr. Song, don't misunderstand.
السيد سونغ، لا تسيء الفهم.
Please help me find Zhao Yan soon.
من فضلك ساعدني في العثور على تشاو يان قريبًا.
Then we can call it even.
ثم يمكننا أن نسميها متساوية.
Call it even?
هل تسميها متساوية؟
You slept with me.
لقد نمت معي.
How can we call it even?
كيف يمكننا أن نسميها متساوية؟
I...
أنا...
I didn't sleep with you.
لم أنم معك.
Did you forget what you did to me last night?
هل نسيت ما فعلته بي الليلة الماضية؟
I remember I didn't sleep with you.
أتذكر أنني لم أنم معك.
Stop acting indecently.
توقف عن التصرف بشكل غير لائق.
If you don't want me to act indecently with you,
إذا كنت لا تريد مني أن أتصرف بشكل غير لائق معك،
delete the video now.
احذف الفيديو الآن.
Why do you look for Zhao Yan?
لماذا تبحث عن تشاو يان؟
He owes me money.
إنه مدين لي بالمال.
If you don't tell me the truth,
إذا لم تخبرني الحقيقة،
I can't help you find him.
لا أستطيع مساعدتك في العثور عليه.
If you don't help,
إذا لم تساعد،
I'll find another way.
سأجد طريقة أخرى.
What exactly do you want?
ماذا تريد بالضبط؟
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
(Outpatient) Okay, I got it.
(مريض خارجي) حسنًا، لقد حصلت عليه.
Nian?
لنا؟
Nian.
لنا.
Open the door, Nian.
افتح الباب، نيان.
He's connected to my mom's death.
إنه مرتبط بوفاة أمي.
Is that enough?
هل هذا يكفي؟
Nian, open the door.
نيان، افتح الباب.
Delete the video.
حذف الفيديو
Then I'll help you find him.
سأساعدك في العثور عليه.
Nian.
لنا.
There was never a video.
لم يكن هناك فيديو أبدًا.
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
you're something.
أنت شيء ما.
Your trick never fails.
حيلتك لن تفشل أبدًا.
When can you find him?
متى يمكنك العثور عليه؟
I only agreed to look for him
لقد وافقت فقط على البحث عنه
but not to find him.
ولكن لم أجده.
You lied to me again.
لقد كذبت علي مرة أخرى.
Open the door, Nian.
افتح الباب، نيان.
So did you.
لقد فعلت ذلك أيضًا.
What else do you want?
ماذا تريد ايضا؟
Open the door!
افتح الباب!
Song Qian,
سونغ تشيان،
open the door.
افتح الباب.
You like him?
هل يعجبك؟
I thought you liked that guy named K.
اعتقدت أنك تحب هذا الرجل الذي يدعى ك.
Yes,
نعم،
I do like him.
انا احبه.
But who I like has nothing to do with you, right?
لكن من أحب لا علاقة له بك، أليس كذلك؟
You're not K.
أنت لست ك.
Open the door, Nian.
افتح الباب، نيان.
Song Qian, let me be clear.
سونغ تشيان، دعني أكون واضحا.
You have a fiancée.
لديك خطيبة.
Avoid actions that cause misunderstandings.
تجنب الأفعال التي تسبب سوء الفهم.
Okay?
تمام؟
♪Without your company♪
♪بدون شركتك♪
♪I'm truly not used to it♪
♪أنا لست معتادًا على ذلك حقًا♪
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Nian,
لنا،
are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Weiwei and I looked for you all night.
لقد بحثنا أنا وويوي عنك طوال الليل.
Did you and he...
هل أنت وهو...؟
I have nothing to do with him.
ليس لي علاقة به.
(Didn't I warn you)
(ألم أحذرك)
(not to develop any feelings for me?)
(لا تتطور أي مشاعر تجاهي؟)
Even if I had feelings for you,
حتى لو كان لدي مشاعر تجاهك،
we could never be together.
لن نتمكن من أن نكون معًا أبدًا.
We've faked an amnesia case for you.
لقد قمنا بتزوير قضية فقدان الذاكرة بالنسبة لك.
Your identity now is Song Qian.
هويتك الآن هي سونغ تشيان.
(Make sure)
(تأكد)
(to sever the past.)
(لقطع الماضي.)
(Or you'll be in great danger.)
(أو سوف تكون في خطر كبير.)
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
why harass him again?
لماذا تضايقه مرة أخرى؟
Next one.
التالي.
Dr. Gu, the chief wants to see you.
الدكتور جو، الرئيس يريد رؤيتك.
(Why would the chief ask me to come to the warehouse?)
(لماذا يطلب مني الرئيس الحضور إلى المستودع؟)
Who are you?
من أنت؟
How did you get in?
كيف دخلت؟
Gu Nian,
قو نيان,
you've offended someone you shouldn't have.
لقد أسأت إلى شخص ما وكان لا ينبغي عليك ذلك.
Someone paid for your life.
لقد دفع شخص ما ثمن حياتك.
You can't escape.
لا يمكنك الهروب.
Let me go.
دعني أذهب.
And I'll pay you double.
وسأدفع لك ضعف المبلغ.
No matter how much you pay today, you won't leave alive.
مهما دفعت اليوم فلن تخرج حياً.
Get her.
احصل عليها.
If I must die,
إذا كان لا بد لي من الموت،
tell me who sent you.
أخبرني من أرسلك.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I can tell you.
أستطيع أن أخبرك.
You seduced her fiancé.
لقد أغويت خطيبها.
(Wei Qing?)
(وي تشينغ؟)
Tie her up.
ربطها.
I've recorded everything
لقد سجلت كل شيء
you said.
أنت قلت.
If you kill me,
إذا قتلتني
it'll be uploaded to the cloud.
سيتم تحميله إلى السحابة.
The police will know you killed me by then.
سوف تعرف الشرطة أنك قتلتني بحلول ذلك الوقت.
But if you let me go,
ولكن إذا سمحت لي بالذهاب،
I'll delete the recording.
سأحذف التسجيل.
Why did you start a fire?
لماذا أشعلت النار؟
Boss, we didn't do it.
يا رئيس، نحن لم نفعل ذلك.
It's on fire.
إنها تحترق.
Let's go! Hurry!
هيا بنا! أسرع!
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Today's meeting is over.
إنتهى إجتماع اليوم.
Mr. Song, bad news.
السيد سونغ، أخبار سيئة.
Our warehouse with the hospital is on fire.
مستودعنا مع المستشفى يحترق.
What? Okay.
ماذا؟حسنا.
Nian!
لنا!
Nian, just wait.
نيان، فقط انتظر.
Help is on the way.
المساعدة في الطريق.
Move!
يتحرك!
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
Gu Nian?
قو نيان؟
♪From your mouth, I find it hard to describe♪
♪من فمك، أجد صعوبة في وصفه♪
Gu Nian.
قو نيان.
Wake up!
استيقظ!
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
Qian!
تشيان!
What are you doing? Don't go in.
ماذا تفعل؟ لا تدخل.
- Come out. - Let me go!
- اخرج. - دعني أذهب!
Brother, save Qian.
أخي، أنقذ تشيان.
Shut up!
اسكت!
Qian!
تشيان!
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
Qian,
تشيان،
was saving Gu Nian worth your life?
هل كان إنقاذ قو نيان يستحق حياتك؟
You instigated the warehouse fire, didn't you?
لقد قمت بإشعال حريق المستودع، أليس كذلك؟
Have you ever thought
هل فكرت يوما
how much trouble that would cause
كم من المشاكل التي قد يسببها ذلك
if she died there?
إذا ماتت هناك؟
Qian,
تشيان،
how could you think that of me?
كيف يمكنك أن تفكر بي هكذا؟
I couldn't?
لم أستطع؟
I caught the people who set the fire.
لقد ألقي القبض على الأشخاص الذين أشعلوا النار.
They said you instructed them.
قالوا أنك أعطيتهم التعليمات.
She's been harassing you.
لقد كانت تضايقك.
You had people set the fire just because of that?
لقد جعلت الناس يشعلون النار فقط بسبب ذلك؟
I just wanted to scare her.
أردت فقط تخويفه.
To scare her?
لتخويفها؟
If I hadn't arrived in time,
لو لم أصل في الوقت المناسب،
she'd have died.
لقد كانت ستموت.
You care about her so much?
هل تهتم بها كثيرًا؟
I don't care about her.
لا أهتم بها.
I'm worried about you.
أنا قلق عليك.
Do you know instigating arson can land you in prison?
هل تعلم أن التحريض على الحرق العمد قد يؤدي بك إلى السجن؟
No, it won't.
لا، لن يحدث ذلك.
My brother will cover it for me.
أخي سوف يغطيها لي.
If the police find evidence,
إذا وجدت الشرطة أدلة،
he can't help you.
لا يستطيع مساعدتك.
I only told Li Yong to scare her.
لقد طلبت من لي يونغ فقط أن يخيفها.
I didn't instigate arson.
لم أقم بالتحريض على الحرق.
Qian, believe me.
تشيان، صدقيني.
I didn't want to kill her.
لم أكن أريد قتلها.
I don't want jail time.
لا أريد قضاء وقت في السجن.
Help me.
ساعدني.
(She doesn't seem to lie.)
(لا يبدو أنها تكذب.)
(If it's not her,)
(إذا لم تكن هي)
(who exactly wants to harm Gu Nian?)
(من يريد أن يؤذي قو نيان بالضبط؟)
(Yesterday, there was a fire at the Wei Group's warehouse.)
(أمس، وقع حريق في مستودع مجموعة وي.)
(A trapped women was rescued in time.)
(تم إنقاذ المرأة المحاصرة في الوقت المناسب.)
(Police found large traces of gasoline around the warehouse.)
(عثرت الشرطة على آثار كبيرة من البنزين حول المستودع.)
(Preliminary police assessment)
(التقييم الأولي للشرطة)
(suspected arson.)
(يشتبه في أنه حريق متعمد.)
Gu Nian.
قو نيان.
♪What is secretly stirring♪
♪ما الذي يتحرك سرا♪
♪From your mouth, I find it hard to describe♪
♪من فمك، أجد صعوبة في وصفه♪
♪What praises can disappear in just a second♪
♪ما هي الثناءات التي يمكن أن تختفي في ثانية واحدة♪
♪Vanishing without a trace♪
♪الاختفاء دون أثر♪
♪Waving hands to break free from the splendid cage♪
♪تلويح الأيدي للتحرر من القفص الرائع♪
♪Words against the heart, a pain slashes through the sky♪
♪كلمات ضد القلب، ألم يشق السماء♪
♪Floating into the endless night sky, the wind fierce and strong♪
♪تطفو في سماء الليل اللامتناهية، والرياح شرسة وقوية♪
♪Who is reckless, continuing to lose control, with impunity♪
♪من هو المتهور، الذي يستمر في فقدان السيطرة، مع الإفلات من العقاب♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is pulling the strings behind♪
♪لا أستطيع أن أرى من يسحب الخيوط من الخلف♪
♪The wound still aches, and the memory is not yet over♪
♪الجرح لا يزال يؤلمني، والذكرى لم تنته بعد♪
♪There are two endings, whether you understand or not♪
♪هناك نهايتان، سواء فهمت أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪
♪Cannot see who is tracking from behind♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية من يتتبعني من الخلف♪
♪The heart still beats, total blood-red before my eyes♪
♪لا يزال القلب ينبض، أحمر اللون كالدم أمام عيني♪
♪Only one ending remains, whether it helps or not♪
♪تبقى نهاية واحدة فقط، سواء كانت مفيدة أم لا♪
♪Let me disappear into the darkness♪
♪دعني أختفي في الظلام♪